123employee.com 2013-09-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

**IP Addresses:**  
We may use your IP address to help diagnose any problems with the 123EMPLOYEE website or server, and for any general admin of our site. Your IP address, should you decide to register for the 123Employee, is also used to help prevent you from creating a duplicate account.

**Cookies:**  
When you first visit the 123Employee site, a ‘cookie’ is sent to your computer. A cookie is a tiny file that identifies you as a unique user. It stores personal preferences and user data, in no way does this tell us who you are. We use cookies to track special offers and promotions that may be presented to you as you navigate our website. This is done so that you are not presented with the same special offers or promotions more than once, or after you have indicated you don’t have an interest. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent.

**Information Dissemination:**  
We may use information that you supply to us to bring selected offers to our members via email.

**Links to Other Sites:**  
123Employee.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame of content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party. Please be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of 123Employee.com and this policy.

**Children Under 13:**  
123Employee.com does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe 123Employee.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

**Security:**  
This web site has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and/or alteration of the information that you provide. Furthermore, we have taken every precaution technically possible to prevent any unauthorized access to the contents of this web server.

**Contact:**  
You agree that you give 123Employee the right to contact you via, email, phone or by any means.  You will have the option to opt out of any and all correspondence at any time.

**Contacting 123Employee:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact us.

**Policy Changes:**  
123Employee reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time.This Privacy Policy was last revised on April 7, 2009.

**Contact:**  
You agree that you give 123Employee the right to contact you via, email, phone or by any means. You will have the option to opt out of any and all correspondence at any time.
